# Rory Simmonds

07739 519 483 rory@blankbox.business

## **About**

With over a decades experience in management roles, I have built a design agency alongside my Business Partner that has services hundreds of clients across the UK and Europe.

I have consistently prioritised self-improvement, completing further education courses in Digital Marketing, Mathematics and Front-End Development.

## **Experience**

### Blank Box Ltd / Director AUG 2018 - PRESENT

I work as the Director of Blank Box Ltd, a design agency specialising in web design and branding. I manage all areas of the business alongside my business partner.

# Big Group / Account Manager JUL 2016 - AUG 2018

Working on blue-chip accounts to provide digital management solutions, graphic design and print. I also completed a four-month secondment with Motorola to co-ordinate with sales teams across Motorola EMEA to develop a suite of sales analytics reports for the EMEA Director of Retail.

#### Benchmark Fabrications / Project Manager FEB 2014 - JUL 2016

Managing the maintenance of Samsung's Retail estate in the UK and ROI. I co-ordinated a team of five Engineers to maintain the estate, using in-house software to manage all work and report to the client. I managed the sale, development and administration of the software to the client.

## **Education**

edX / Front-End Development Bootcamp 2023 - 2024

An intensive 16 week bootcamp in Front-End Development

Oxford College of Marketing / Digital Marketing Diploma 2013 - 2015

A long-distance course with the Oxford College of Marketing to the level of Higher National Degree, with a result of Merit.

A Levels / Maths, Business Studies, IT, English Literature 2009 - 2011 & 2013 - 2015

A-levels studied at Stratford Upon Avon in 2009, and Oxford Open Learning trust in 2016, with a result of B in IT, and an A in all remaining subjects.

#### References